□ 720-326-5046 | ■ ethanholen@gmail.com | 😭 ethanholen.com | 🖸 EthanHolen | 🛅 ethan-holen-563856174

Summary_

Current IOS Developer, and undergraduate at Colorado State University with experience in both the software and hardware side of the tech industry as well as the medical field. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys backpacking, mountain biking and camping in the wilds of Colorado. Interested in gaining new and interesting experiences in the field of Computer Science.

Education

COLORADO STATE UNIVERSITY(COLLEGE OF NATURAL SCIENCES)

Fort Collins, CO

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Jan. 2019 - PRESENT

• Relevant Coursework: Intro to Java Programming (Java)

SAINT LOUIS UNIVERSITY (COLLEGE OF ARTS AND SCIENCES)

Saint Louis, MO

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, PRE MED

Valor Christian High School

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2018

• Relevant Coursework: Managing Big Data (Python)

Highlands Ranch, CO

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Aug. 2014 - May. 2018

• Relevant Coursework: AP Computer Science (Java)

Work Experience

Valor Christian High School

Highlands Ranch, CO.

IT INTERN

Aug. 2016 - May. 2018

- Provided hardware and software solutions for help desk tickets
- Helped manage a JAMF environment of 550 Apple devices
- · Setup and management of 20 Aerohive network access points

Express Care Cheyenne, WY

MEDICAL ASSISTANT

May. 2016 - Jul. 2016

May. 2019 - Present

- Assisted Doctor or PA on call as a scribe
- · Vitals and initial patient charts
- · Strep, urine and vision tests

IOS Development Denver CO

IOS DEVELOPER

- Wrote custom IOS Application for Douglas County Sheriffs Office
- Designed and Created a secure back-end using AWS Lambda and API Gateway

Extracurricular Activity

Skills & Talents

PERSONAL

- · Programming Languages: Java, Python, HTML, CSS, Bash, Swift
- · Software: OSX, Windows, Linux, AWS, Xcode, Personal Website
- · Hardware: Custom PC, Mac Repairs, Raspberry Pi

Eagle Scout - Troop 102

Greenwood Village, CO

PATROL LEADER, TROOP HISTORIAN

Sep. 2011 - May. 2015

- Learned Leadership and organization through positions of patrol leader and troop historian
- · Project: Build garden and fence around local monastery

Medical Missions Work

MEDICAL ASSISTANT

Ethiopia Aug. 2017

• Assisted physicians with scribe work and basic medical tests.

• Video: https://govalor.com/discovery-ethiopia-video/

ETHAN HOLEN · RÉSUMÉ AUGUST 17, 2019